- # We # - # Are the Crystal #
- # Gems # - # we'll always save the day #
♪ and if you think we can't ♪
♪ we'll always find a way ♪
- # that's why the people # - # of this world #
♪ believe in... Garnet ♪
- # Amethyst # - # and Pearl #
♪ And Steven! ♪
再次谢谢你们在我离开的时候
Thanks again for protecting Beach City
保护了海滩市,康妮
while I was gone, Connie.
没关系,既然你已经从太空回来了
No problem. And now that you're back from space,
那我就正式转让我对你的床的控制权
I officially relinquish control of your bed to you.
谢谢你帮我暖被窝,长官
Thank you for keeping it warm, sir.
我也希望你爹能喜欢新的洗车店招牌
I hope your dad liked the new car wash sign.
他喜欢死了
He loved it.
相信招牌挂起来之后
I'm sure it'll look great
一定会很好看的
when the Gems are done putting it up.
我希望宝石们能在我走之前回来,好告个别
I hope they're back in time for me to say bye.
呃...可能要等好一会儿了
Uh... It might be a while.
你根本想不到让她们一起做事
You wouldn't believe how many of them it takes
是有多困难呢
to screw in a light bulb.
我在想我妈到哪儿了
I wonder where my mom is.
她早该来接我了
She should have been here to pick me up by now.
这里是麦雪仑医生
You've reached Dr. Maheswaran.
请留言,如果你是我的病人的话
Please leave a message, and if you're one of my patients,
你不该有这个号码的!
you shouldn't have this number!
她不接电话
She's not answering.
这个,想想好的一面!
Well, look on the bright side!
现在咱俩能多玩一会儿了
Now we can hang out a little longer.
我相信她肯定会来的
I'm sure she'll show up eventually.
我不是特别想缠着你
I don't want to impose.
我意思是,你脑袋里肯定很乱
I mean, you must have a lot to think about
毕竟刚经过了太空冒险
after your space adventure.
你还差点弄丢了你爹
You almost lost your dad,
还有这些关于钻石们和你妈妈的事...
and all that stuff about the diamonds and your mom...
如果你想要点私人空间的话我也能理解
I'd understand if you need some space.
才不,现在我最怕的就是"空间"了
Nah, the last thing I need right now is more space.
好吧
Okay.
所以现在你想玩什么?
So what do you want to do?
最后这词是个名词
The last word is a noun.
呃,多层游轮
Um, multi-hulled watercraft.
好,句子完成了
Okay, here it goes.
"摇摆的糕点师烤出了古怪的糕点
"The wiggly baker baked some new wacky pastries.
有蜗牛泡芙
There were snail puffs,
割草机派,还有熵玛芬"
lawnmower pies, and entropy muffins."
"大家都毛茸茸的
"Everyone was so fuzzy
他们把所有东西都吃了,包括一个
that they ate everything ... even the cheesecake
多层游轮形状的芝士蛋糕"
shaped like a multi-hulled watercraft."
太奇怪了
This is really weird.
我妈从来没有不接电话过
My mom always answers her phone.
嗯
Hmm.
哦 我用狮子载你回家如何?
Oh. How about I give you a ride home on Lion?
我不是特别担心回不回家
It's not getting home I'm worried about.
要是我们在路上相互错过了怎么办?
What if she shows up here and we're gone?
我们应该待在这里等她来
We should probably stay put until she comes.
好吧 ,反正也是等着
Well, while we're still waiting,
再来一局怪句子游戏吧?
how about another weird word game?
好吧
Okay.
好,我们现在需要
All right, let's see what we got here.
第一个词是个形容词
First one is an adjective.
"意外的"
Accidental.
下一个是个名词
And the next one's a noun.
"事故"
Mishap.
状语?
Adverb?
"未预料地"
Unexpectedly.
过去时态动词?
Past tense verb?
"撞毁"
Crashed.
名词?
Noun?
"爆炸"
Explosion.
哇哦,你真的很担心你妈妈啊,是吧?
Wow, you're really worried about your mom, huh?
是啊,她从来都没有迟到过
Yeah. It's just she's never late for anything.
有人吗?
Hello?
我进来了
I'm coming in.
康妮!
Connie!
妈妈!
Mom!
妈妈,出什么事了?
Mom, what happened?
我一直给你打电话,你就是不接
I kept calling, but you weren't answering.
我都快吓坏了
I was starting to freak out.
这个手术时间太长了
Well, surgery went long,
然后我又得替斯汤堡医生加班
and then I had to cover for Dr. Stromberg, again.
我手机也没电了,我怀疑我的一个病人
My phone died, and I suspect one of my patients
偷了我的充电器...
stole my charger and...
真的太对不起了,康妮
I'm so sorry, Connie.
没关系,妈妈
It's okay, Mom.
现在一切都好了
Everything's fine now.
谢谢你接待康妮到这么晚
Thank you for letting Connie stay late.
晚安,史蒂文!
Night, Steven!
晚安,康妮
Night, Connie.
所以他刚蒸桑拿回来?
So he's back from the spa, huh?
他刚从太空回来啦
No. I said space.
哈
Huh.
啊,这才叫爽
Aw, that's nice.
你造,有时候我会在想在墙上微笑的
You know, sometimes I wonder if it's even you up there...
是不是真正的你
smiling all day and night.
我就是想了解真正的你
I just want to know the real you.
而不是从别人的话语中了解你
Not the you that everyone tells me about.
我就是想知道事情的真相
I just want to know the truth.
呃,你好啊,房间
Uh... Hey, room.
好久不见了,是吧?
It's been a bit, huh?
那片云是你新做的?
Is that a new cloud?
呃...
Uh...
这个...
So...
我想你一定在好奇我为什么来这儿
I suppose you're wondering why I'm here.
我知道这里的东西都不是真的,但是...
I know nothing in here is real, but...
我想见见我妈妈
but I want to see my mom.
你好,史蒂文
Hello, Steven.
呃,这个...
Um, it's...
见到你很高兴
It's nice to meet you.
我也很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you, too.
呃,不好意思
Um, sorry.
对我来说感觉有点奇怪
This is a little weird for me.
没关系的
That's okay.
所以你现在想干嘛?
So what do you want to do?
哦,呃...
Oh, uh...
我还没想过这么远
I guess I hadn't thought that far ahead.
你喜欢电子游戏吗?
Do you like video games?
给我讲讲游戏规则吧,史蒂文
So, tell me about this game, Steven.
这个,这是个扳手腕游戏
Well, I guess it's an arm-wrestling simulator,
是个山寨版的格斗游戏
which is spin-off of a fighting game,
那个格斗游戏又是个武侠剧的同人游戏
based on a show about a lonely swordsman that I like.
这样解释起来就很困难了
It's kind of weird and hard to explain,
但是我喜欢
but that's why I like it.
听起来真的不能再好
That sounds just marvelous.
K-O!
棒,我赢了!
Yeah, I won!
棒,你赢了!
Yay, you won.
还有什么亲子互动的活动来着?
What else do kids do with their parents?
接得好,儿子
Nice catch, son.
真有趣
This is fun.
也许打棒球会更好?
Or would baseball be better?
史蒂文,所有的体育运动都很美妙
Steven, all sports are beautiful.
每个运动都是独特的体验
Each sport is a unique experience.
肾上腺素的激发,对荣耀的追寻,力和美的展现
The adrenaline, the glory, the sheer feats of athleticism.
每个运动都是那么复杂,但又有着全同的原则
Each one so complicated and yet exactly the same.
哇
Whoa.
嘿,史蒂文!
Hey, Steven!
你造,我总感觉我的青春期
You know, I've always felt like something was unusual
有缺少点什么东西
about my adolescence.
也许我一直以来缺的就是...橄榄球
Maybe this is what I've been missing ... football.
触地得分!
Touchdown!
史蒂文...
Steven...
我这段时间来 一直都在想你
I've been, uh, thinking about you...
比以往更想你
a lot lately ... more than usual.
是吗?
Is that so?
是啊,我一生以来
Yeah, well, for my whole life,
听过很多你的故事
I've been hearing stories about you.
关于你是多么美丽动人的故事
About how amazing you were,
关于你善良有爱心的故事
that you were so kind and loving.
每次看到你挂在墙上的
And every time I'd see the painting of you
那幅画像,我都能被激励到
hanging in the temple, I'd be inspired...
也会想起身上肩负的责任
and reminded of how much I had to live up to.
我,呃...
I, uh...
我甚至想过把头发染成粉的...还不止一次想过
I've even thought about dyeing my hair pink ... more than once.
你现在的发色就挺好的
There's nothing wrong with your hair.
保持原样就很好
It's wonderful just the way it is.
各种意义上都很好,就像你一样
Wonderful in every way, just like you.
哇,这还真好
Wow. This is nice.
真的...太好了
It's ... it's really nice.
我...我真的早就该
I ... I should have tried this
来这里试试了
a long time ago.
但是,史蒂文,你意识到了吗?
But, Steven, don't you realize?
我们一直以来其实都在一起
We've been together this whole time.
哦
Oh.
是...是...是这样的
That's ... that ... that's right.
哦
Oh.
这是我们第一次在一起
This is the first time we've hung out together.
我得留影做纪念
I got to capture this moment.
除了我之外什么都没有啊
There's nothing here but me.
我一直都在自言自语吗
I'm just talking to myself.
你不是我妈妈
You're not my mom.
我不是?
I'm not?
你只是我对你的印象和想象
This is how I want you to be,
我还是没了解真正的你
but I don't know if this is who you really are.
我知道你的很多事
I've learned things about you,
那些你藏作秘密的事
things you wanted to keep secret.
你把铋斯姆关进了狮子里
You locked Bismuth away inside Lion
因为她想粉碎别的宝石
because she wanted to shatter Gems,
你还从来没有告诉过石榴和珍珠
and you never told Garnet or Pearl.
然后你又粉碎了粉钻
But then you shattered pink diamond.
导致现在母星盯上了地球
Now all of Homeworld has it out for Earth
还有我和水晶宝石们!
and the Crystal Gems and me!
你把我们都拉进了危机中,然后又自顾自消失了!
You put us all in danger, and you just disappeared!
哇 哇
Whoa. Whoa.
我终于知道真相了
I finally know the truth.
我知道你真面目了
I know what you are.
你是个骗子!
You're a liar!
我以为你从来不想伤害别人的
I thought you never wanted to hurt anyone,
但是你伤害了所有人!
but you hurt everyone!
你怎么能抛下石榴紫晶和珍珠
How could you just leave Garnet and Amethyst and Pearl
还有...还有老爸?
and ... and Dad?
她们离了你根本不知所措!
They don't know what to do without you!
也许她们根本在你心中
Maybe they didn't matter to you as much as
还没有藏起你那些破事重要!
hiding from the mess you made!
这就是我存在的原因,对吧?
And that's why I'm here, isn't it?
你创造了我只是为了
Did you make me just so you wouldn't have to
让我处理你犯下的错误?
deal with all your mistakes?
我存在的目的就是这个吗?
Is that all I'm here for?
史蒂文,你知道根本不是这样的
Steven, you know that isn't true.
我留给你的录像带里,我告诉过你
In the tape I left you, I told you how much
我是多想让你存在在这个世界上
I wanted to have you and let you exist.
你觉得我在录像带里说的话都是谎言吗?
Do you think what I said to you in the tape was a lie?
不 我很确定
No. I'm sure ...
我很确定你说的都是真心话
I'm sure you meant it.
我明白了
I get it.
我知道你不是有意让我处理你的错误
I know you didn't want me to deal with your problems.
但是你现在是我的一部分了
But you're a part of me now,
我现在得对付你留下的那些事了
and I have to deal with what you left behind.
嘿,史嘟宝!
Hey, Shtu-ball!
猜猜谁买了牛仔短裤
Guess who's back in jean shorts.
猜猜谁给你带了披萨
And guess who also got you a pizza.
-就是我!-老爸!
- It was me! - Dad!
紫晶!石榴!
Amethyst! Garnet!
还有珍珠?
And Pearl, too?
辣肠披萨卖完了
They were all out of pepperoni, by the way,
我只能给你带蘑菇的了
so I just got you mushroom.
-希望你不介意吧 -简直完美
- I hope that's all right. - It's perfect.